<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.4//EN"
  "/usr/share/sgml/docbook/xml-dtd-4.3-1.0-25/docbookx.dtd">
 
<article>

  <articleinfo>
    <title>EPICS Lakeshore 340 Support Module User Guide</title>
    <copyright>
      <year>2007</year>
      <holder>Copyright 2007 Diamond Light Source Limited</holder>
    </copyright>
  </articleinfo>

  <sect1>
      <title>Trouble Shooting</title>
    

      <sect2>
      <title>IO Status shows TIMEOUT - Device not responding</title>
      <para>If the Interaface Control is in the On state but the device does not respond to the regular reading of the filter position
      then the interface will display the value TIMEOUT in the IO Status field. The interface still behaves as normal but that the 
      change int the desired filter position will not cause an actual change in position. The Filter field will show the value that
      was last read successfully.</para>
      <itemizedlist mark='opencircle'>
      <listitem><para>Check that the device is powered on and is controllable by the front panel button</para></listitem>
      <listitem><para>Check that the serial cable is connected to the device.</para></listitem>
      <listitem><para>Try powering the device on and off.</para></listitem>
	  </itemizedlist>
	  </sect2>
      <sect2>
      <title>STB or ESR do not show 0</title>
      <para>STB is the Status Byte read from the device</para>
      <para>Response: 00 indicates no error</para>
      <para>32 decimal ; 20 Hex / bit5 ; indicate an error condition</para>
      <para>ESR is the value of the Event Status Register read when the STB last read 0</para>
	  <para>80 - The 74041 has been power on reset since last read</para>
	  <para>20 - The 74041 has received an illegal command</para>
      <para>10 - The 74041 had a problem with the filter wheel</para>
	  <para>Press the reset button is STB is now 0 to clear the latched value of the ESR</para>
	  </sect2>
      <sect2>
      <title>Filter is shown as unkown when Interface Control is On</title>
      <para>No valid filter erading has yet been made of the device</para>
      <itemizedlist mark='opencircle'>
      <listitem><para>Physically check that the filter wheel is connected to the controller.</para></listitem>
	  </itemizedlist>
 	  </sect2>
  </sect1>    
</article>
